KIM SU-YEONG
We have to walk from here.
Yeong-su.
We have to go.
We have to take Su-yeong.
She can't come.
Then I'm not going!
Yeong-su…
I'll also die anyway.
You'll turn into a monster too!
That's not true.
Why would I?
Go away!
I'm staying with Su-yeong!
Go!
Let go!
Let go of me!
I'm not going!
I said I'm not going!
Su-yeong!
Take Su-yeong with us!
Take her with us!
Su-yeong!
I said I'm not going!
Su-yeong…
ORIGINAL STORY WEBTOON SWEET HOME
BY CARNBY KIM AND YOUNGCHAN HWANG
SWEET HOME
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
Damn it.
I would've cooperated
if you had just asked me.
I don't have much time.
That briefcase looks familiar.
Aren't you glad?
I know it's very important to you.
Yes, I am.
You actually managed to find it.
Where did you find it?
Did you kill the person who had it?
I assume they paid their price.
Why?
Do you know this person?
Of course not.
You all know how upset I was
when I lost this.
Open it up.
Why?
What, are you going to use it?
Just for you guys?
Shut up and open it!
The Central Command's safety
is crucial for the country's future!
Pretty fancy way to say you're scared.
I didn't say I wouldn't.
Sure you won't regret it?
You said it stops monsterization.
That's been confirmed.
In a broad sense, yes.
But there's still some figuring out to do.
And I feel kind of pressured
by all the anticipation--
Your job was simply
to create what's in the case.
Of course.
Here we go.
What the hell?
Is this your doing?
Where did you hide it?
A safe place.
Somewhere you could never…
find it.
Hey, kid.
Wake up.
Come on, wake up.
You'll have to excuse me here.
Aren't you coming with us?
I'm a soldier.
I have to return to my base.
You're going back?
Come with us.
You could just ditch your uniform.
They're not going to come for you.
Don't say that.
Desertion is a serious crime.
I'll talk to the soldiers here
and figure something out.
Keep moving in an orderly fashion.
Pull your mask down
so we can check for symptoms.
You have to put that down.
Get your hands off me.
Put it down.
Let go.
Grab him. Check his bag.
It's a gun, sir!
Put him in isolation.
Get over here.
-Let go, you assholes!
-Get over here.
Get him out of here.
Come on. Move it.
Keep moving.
I'm Private Park Chan-yeong
from the 7th Division, 9th Regiment.
I left the base during an operation.
I'll wait for your orders.
Black Kite, we have a returning soldier.
He's Private Park Chan-yeong
from the 7th Division, 9th Regiment.
PITCHER
PARK CHAN-YEONG
BAMSEOM EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT BUREAU
RESTRICTED MILITARY AREA
What's going on?
Sergeant First Class Lee Gi-baek…
and Staff Sergeant Kim Dae-un…
are dead.
They could've lived.
But those motherfuckers…
didn't do anything to help them.
They told us to go to the shelter.
What the hell does that mean?
They're getting us fucking discharged.
As of 12:00 p.m. today,
the whole platoon is to be discharged.
You established the unit yourself,
Brigadier General Han.
You said…
you would never turn your back on us.
That's why we responded to your call.
You're right.
I did say that.
Why are you doing this?
We no longer need the Crow Platoon.
We keep wiping them out,
but there's always more.
So?
Have you given up?
No, I made a choice.
Master Sergeant Tak.
In-hwan.
Be a deserter.
The nation's never thanked you
for your service.
Grab some weapons and food
and get out of here with your men.
You want us…
to dishonor ourselves
and go to the shelter?
No.
Not there.
You can't go there.
What are you hiding, sir?
SHELTER ADMISSION PROTOCOL
1. CHECK TEMPERATURE
2. CHECK FOR MONSTERIZATION SYMPTOMS
Move.
What?
Do it one more time. It must be a mistake.
It's a mistake! I'm not sick!
Let go!
I'm clean! Let go of me!
Fucking let go of me!
-Let go! I'm clean!
-Open the gate!
Open the gate!
-I want out!
-What the hell?
Open up, you assholes!
NOT ADMISSIBLE
Have you had a nosebleed
or a fever recently?
Look at me.
This is an announcement
regarding an update in protocol.
We will no longer be screening survivors.
Please enter in an orderly fashion.
I repeat.
We will no longer be screening survivors.
Please enter in an orderly fashion.
Bang Jin-ho.
Yes, sir.
Aren't you going home?
I haven't heard
from Master Sergeant Tak yet.
That Master Sergeant Tak
who doesn't care about his men's deaths?
Don't talk about him like that, sir.
What?
We're from different units,
but we're in the same one now.
I acknowledge you as my superior.
So please do the same
for Master Sergeant Tak.
Stop being an idiot.
I know you look up to him.
But he doesn't deserve it.
Because people say
he murdered his own family?
That's only a rumor.
It doesn't matter if it's true or not.
Because in my eyes,
he seems like he's capable of it.
Tell me.
Where did you hide it?
Why would I tell you?
I went through so much to hide it.
You must not value your life.
Like you're going to kill me.
I know where the vaccine is.
Why don't we forget about it all
and start over?
You can't fool me again.
I gave you more than enough time.
How dare you
repay my generosity like this?
I told you.
I don't have much time!
Mr. Prime Minister!
That's only the beginning, Dr. Lim.
Let's not waste any more energy, okay?
Now, tell me.
Where did you hide it?
What are you hiding, sir?
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENT
TOP SECRET
Sergeant Kim.
The Crow Platoon's being summoned.
What's going on?
Kim Yeong-hu.
I made up my mind.
Get your head on straight from now on.
About your theory, Dr. Lim.
If monsterization is a natural phenomenon
as you suggested,
I realized that it won't stop
until all of mankind
is dead and gone.
That's why I have a gift for you.
If you don't disappoint me, that is.
What the hell are you going to do?
Clean up.
PLEASE COOPERATE WITH THE MILITARY
TO RESTORE ORDER AND SAFETY
We'll clean them out
before they turn into monsters.
Then the world will be clean
for the time being…
and it might put an end
to this catastrophe.
What should I do, Dr. Lim?
Why are you laughing?
I love it.
That's exactly…
what I wanted.
This is what I wanted to do.
We should've cleaned up regularly!
Everyone…
Everyone lived in peace for too long.
That's why this happened.
What are you waiting for?
Do it.
Clean up.
What about you then?
I'll tell you
where to find what you want.
Sure.
Let's do some cleaning.
What the hell?
Why are those flying this way?
There must be a mistake.
It's coming.
It's coming!
Ji-su!
Yoon Ji-su!
You're not going to talk, are you?
It's going to take some time,
but I'll eventually find it.
No, you'll never find it.
There's a problem I haven't solved yet.
It's too bad, Mr. Prime Minister.
Goodbye then.
Move, Jong-hyun!
It's done, sir.
We'll blow up the isolation area first.
The rest of you, grab the medical supplies
and get ready to head to the shelter.
What do you desire?
I don't know.
Do you think you can resist it?
What happened to your family?
They all died.
Did you kill them?
Have you killed a human before?
Why did you kill… What do you desire?
-Stop it.
-What happened to… Did you kill them?
So what are you now?
Are you human?
Or are you a monster?
I'm talking to you.
Answer me.
How did you like it here?
Was it better than you thought?
Or was it hell?
You set out to help mankind…
and look how you ended up.
Isn't it pathetic?
What do you think I'll do to you?
Will I rescue you again?
Or will I kill you this time?
It's neither.
I'm going to abandon you.
Stay locked up
and watch this place crumble
with your own eyes.
Wake up, Jung Ui-myeong.
Just admit it.
You're a monster.
Yes.
I am a monster.
I told you it was pointless.
I gave you another chance
because it was your first time.
But you threw it away.
You tricked me into
doing some stupid shit.
But not anymore.
Not anymore.
Not anymore, god damn it.
You don't deserve to be a neohuman.
Wither away here.
No.
Realize that there's no human…
who will come save you or you can protect.
Live in despair.
All alone.
Unable to…
die.
No…
Yeong-su.
Wake up.
Good.
Get up.
Okay. Go.
Go.
Hurry.
Hurry, Yeong-su.
Go on.
Go!
Hurry, Yeong-su!
Stand up!
Go!
Get away, Yeong-su!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Yeong-su, please. Just go!
Go!
Hurry up and go!
Please, Yeong-su.
Hurry.
-Go!
-Ji-su…
-Yoon Ji-su!
Yoon Ji-su!
Yeong-su, please.
Go already, Yeong-su!
Just go!
Hurry up!
Yoon Ji-su!
No, Ji-su!
Please, no!
No!
Ji-su!
No.
No! Please!
No! Ji-su!
No!
No…
Yoon Ji-su!
This will be our base camp.
We don't know what could get in.
Seal off all the exits.
-Yes, sir.
How are we going to secure food?
We don't even have water.
We can always find some.
We'll go out as soon as
things are sorted out.
Don't move!
Wait.
How many of you are here?
About 400.
Okay, we'll be able to accommodate them.
Subtitle translation by Jea-heon Chung
Modify by Blue-Bird™